Tommy West papers, Inclusive: 1975-1998, Bulk: 1991-1995
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Tommy West papers
Inclusive: 1975-1998, Bulk: 1991-1995
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3569
West, Fowler C.
5 folders
This collection contains some of the literary works of journalist Tommy West, as well as a few personal remarks describing West by journalist Ray Bell.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Tommy West worked for the San Antonio Express-News from 1980 December until he retired in 1996 January. West was a writing coach for all editorial departments for about 10 years, working with young writers and at one time producing a monthly newsletter on writing and style. He wrote a general-interest column that appeared on the Sunday op-ed page for four years.
For approximately three years West was senior writer for the Sunday Magazine. He also wrote an area column, "Trails West," on people, places, and legends of South Texas. The column appeared four times a week. West also was assistant city editor and assistant state editor at the Express-News.
In 1975, while working for the Fort Worth Press, West wrote a Page 1 column that appeared daily.
Scope and Content
This collection includes photocopies of some of the writings of journalist Tommy West from 1965 to 1995. This collection also includes limited biographical data in the form of a written biography and eulogy.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in chronological order by newspaper. Currently, the collection is arranged in one series: I. Literary Productions.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3569. Acquired 0-00-00
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
West, Tommy.
Subjects
Journalism.
Genres
Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Essays.
- Literary Productions, 1960-1995, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series contains literary articles written by Tommy West, as well as biographical notes from those that knew him. This series is in good condition.
  - Apollo Mission Clippings (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Apollo Mission Clippings (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fort Worth Press Columns (1 of 2), 1975 August 19-October 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Fort Worth Press Columns (2 of 2), 1975 August 19-October 23 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - San Antonio Express News Feature Columns (1 of 2), 1991 May 26-1995 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - San Antonio Express News Feature Columns (2 of 2), 1991 May 26-1995 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - General Clippings (1 of 3), 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Clippings (2 of 3), 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Clippings (3 of 3), 1960-1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Clippings (1 of 2), 1981, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General Clippings (2 of 2), 1981, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - General, 1965-undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (1 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (2 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (3 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (4 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (5 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (6 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (7 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (8 of 8), 1992 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (1 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (2 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (3 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (4 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (5 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (6 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (7 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - San Antonio Express News Magazine (8 of 8), 1993 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Bound Lariat Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 3 OVZ, Folder 1)